ILGWU Local Publications 5780/169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 2, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Daniel Nisnavitz, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: May 25, 1951.
- Box: 2, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: 30th Anniversary Jubilee Celebration., 1964; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Author: Local 97
    Notes: August 1, 1964.
- Box: 2, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: 60th Anniversary, 1913-1973, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Author: Local 91
- Box: 2, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Local 89, ILGWU, 1919-1944, Jubilee, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Notes: November, 1944. 3 copies, one blue cover and two red covers.
- Box: 2, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Thirty-Fifth Anniversary, Local 91 ILGWU, 1913-1948, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 18, 1948. Second copy.
  - Item 2: Welcome to the 35th Anniversary of Local Ninety One, ILGWU, 1913-1948, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 18, 1948.
  - Item 3: Guest List Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Local Ninety One, ILGWU, 1913-1948, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Testimonial in Honor of Harry Greenberg Marking 35 Years of Service to the Labor Movement., 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: March 15, 1949.
  - Item 5: Forty Years, Local 91., 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 12, 1953.
  - Item 6: Testimonial Dinner Harry Greenberg: Celebrating 40 Years of Service to Local 91., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Box: 2, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: 25 Years With the Dress Makers Union, Local 100, 1916-1941, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Author: Local 100
- Box: 2, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: In the Beginning., Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Our Union, Our Convention, Home Office., 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: May, 1940.
  - Item 3: We Do It Again: Local 91, ILGWU, Annual Report for 1941., Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: To: Local 91, ILGWU, 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: Letters from our Boys and Girls in the Armed Services Here and Abroad.
  - Item 5: My Trip to Europe., 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Notes: November-December 1946. A Report to the Executive Board Local 91
- Box: 2, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Thirty-Fifth Anniversary, Local 91 ILGWU, 1913-1948., Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Box: 2, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Report of Local 91, ILGWU., 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Box: 2, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Local 91, ILGWU, Annual Report, 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Box: 2, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: We Do It Again: Local 91 ILGWU Annual Reprot for 1941, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Box: 2, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: 25th Anniversary: Local 91, ILGWU. Testimonial to Harry Greenberg for 25 Years of Union Service, 1913-1938., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Notes: 4 copies.
- Box: 2, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Our Aim: Local 91 Gives Relief to Members in Need., 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1935:Feb.).
- Box: 2, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Report on an Investigation of Local 91 Shops., 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Author: Charles H. Green
- Box: 2, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary, Local 91, ILGWU, Honoring Our Manager Harry Greenberg for 50 Years of Union Service., 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: December 28, 1963. 2 copies.
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Benjamin Kaplan 60th Birthday: Jubilee Journal., 1956; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Local 117
- Box: 3, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program., 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: Local 142
    Notes: April 25. 1941.
  - Item 2: 20 Years of Progress: The Local 142 Story., 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Souvenir Journal: Friends of Joseph Tuvim Fiftieth Birthday Celebration., 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Notes: September 28, 1946.
  - Item 4: Dinner in Honor of Joseph Tuvim, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Notes: April 12, 1951.
- Box: 3, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Fifteenth Annual Excursion., 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Author: Local 135
    Notes: August 27, 1949.
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Fifteenth Annual Dance., 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Local 134
    Notes: April 23, 1949.
  - Item 2: 16th Annual Dance., 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notes: April 22, 1950.
  - Item 3: 17th Annual Dance.`, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notes: April 14, 1951.
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Mayor John J. Grogan of Hoboken will be the principle speaker at a special Executive Board Meeting of Local 133., 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Local 133
    Notes: December 31, 1953. Press release.
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Twentieth Anniversary Celebration, 1937-1957., Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Local 132
    Notes: March 9, 1957.
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Second Annual Dinner and Dance, Local 130., 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: Local 130
    Notes: March 10, 1951.
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Dance Sponsored by Local 130, Monmouth County., 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 17, 1949.
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Agreement: Rules and By-Laws., Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Author: Local 122
- Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Ladies Garment Carrier., 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Local 102
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1936:Sep.) - v.3:no.5 (1939:Feb.). Oversized on top of folders in box.
  - Item 2: Souvenir Journal: Second Anniversary Jubilee and Testimonial Dinner Tendered to Sau Metz., 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: Christmas Eve, 1934.
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Jubilee Journal: 75th Anniversary of the Cloak Operators' Union and 25 Years of the Merged Cloak Local 117., 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Dinner-Dance., 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Author: Local 150 and Local 157
    Notes: October 1, 1937.
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: General Activities and Finance Reports., 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Information Bulletin., 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: February 1, 1943.
  - Item 2: Information Bulletin., 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Testimonial and Bon-Voyage Dinner to Benjamin Kaplan and Rubin Zuckerman., 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: August 9, 1949.
- Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Algemeyne Tetigkeytn, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Algemeyne Tetigkeytn, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: General Activities and Finance Reports., 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: General Activities and Finance Reports., 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Step by Step, 1941-1966: A Report of 25 Years of Progress. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Local 105
- Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Progress: Our Common Purpose., 1941-1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Good Union Never Rests: A Report on Three Years of Union Growth and Expanding Service., 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: 2 copies
  - Item 2: A Good Union Never Rests: The Story of Our Union., 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Know Your Union: Questions and Answers, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: 3rd edition.
  - Item 4: Know Your Union: Questions and Answers, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: 9th edition.
  - Item 5: New Gains, New Goals., 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Service Tells the Story: Local 105, ILGWU, Tenth Anniversary, 1941-1951, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Fifth Anniversary Dinner and Dance: Progressive Dressmakers, Branch 122., 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Author: Branck 122 Workmen's Circle
    Notes: March 30, 1940.
- Box: 3, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Emancipator., 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Author: Local 188
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1935:Sept.)-v.1:no.24 (1936:Sept.). Bound volume.
- Box: 3, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: 1940 Grand Ball., Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Author: Local 362
    Notes: Movember 2, 1940. Local 362.
- Box: 3, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Fifth Anniversary Dance and Card Party., 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Author: Local 316
    Notes: May 8, 1941.
- Box: 3, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: ILGWU 15: Union des Ouvriers du Vetement pour Dames du Montreal, 1937-1952., Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Author: Local 262
    Language: English;French.
- Box: 3, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Souvenir: Annual Ball., 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Author: Local 246
    Notes: March 13, 1942.
- Box: 3, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Unionette., 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Author: Local 225
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1940:Jan.).
- Box: 3, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: 1935-1950: 15 Years of Progress., Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Author: Local 216
  - Item 2: 1935-1955: 20 Years of Progress., Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Box: 3, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program: 20th Anniversary, 1935-1955., Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: Local 214
    Notes: October 18, 1955.
- Box: 3, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program: First New Year Dance., 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Author: Local 205
    Notes: September 29, 1935.
  - Item 2: Souvenir Program: Annual Dance., 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Notes: February 6, 1938.
- Box: 3, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Fifteenth Anniversary of the Dressmakers' Union, Local 144, ILGWU, Festival and Dance., 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Author: Local 144
    Notes: October 9, 1948.
- Box: 3, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: This is Your Union., 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Author: Local 190
    Notes: April 1960.
- Box: 3, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Testimonial Dinner-Dance Given in Honor of Harry A. Posner., 1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Author: Local 149
    Notes: June 27, 1936.
- Box: 3, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program: First Annual Ball., 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: Local 184
    Notes: June 21, 1935.
- Box: 3, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Programme: 3rd Annual Carnival Dance., 1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Author: Local 182
    Notes: February 14, 1936.
- Box: 3, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Your Union, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: Local 163
- Box: 3, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Helping Hand Fund., 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Local 158
    Notes: Christmas 1948. 2 copies.
- Box: 3, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Union Guide., 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1938:Feb.).
- Box: 3, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Union Guide., 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Local 150
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1936:Jan.)-v.2:no.7 (1937:July).
- Box: 3, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Union Guide., 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1935:Jan.)-v.1:no.8 (1936:Oct.).
- Box: 3, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Union Guide., 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1934:Dec.)-v.1:no.8 (1936:Oct.).
- Box: 3, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Souvenir: Testimonial Banquet and Dance in Honor of Jewett T. Flagg., 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Author: Local 378
    Notes: September 12, 1942. Local 378.
- Box: 3, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: 20 Years of Progress; Sam Kraisman, 70 Years of Accomplishment., 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: Local 199
    Notes: November 20, 1965.
  - Item 2: 20 Years of Progress., 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Box: 4, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 1933-1943 Ten Years: A Study in Progress., Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: Philadelphia Waist and Dressmakers' Union.
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Where's My Raise?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Notes: Eastern Out-Of-Town Department.
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Excerpts fro the Rules and Regulations., 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 1, 1968. Los Angeles Union Health Center.
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bon Voyage Dinner Tendered to Julius Hochman., 1934; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 14, 1934. Joint Board Deressmakers' Union.
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Plain Talk., 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Notes: Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers' Union.
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Bon Voyage Dinner Tendered to Isidore Nagler., 1934; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Notes: July 19, 1934. New York Joint Cloak Board.
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report 1944-1947, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Notes: June 1947. Northeast Department.
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 33rd ILGWU Convention; Norhteast Birthday., 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Notes: Norteast Department.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Journal: Third Annual Grand Ball, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Branch 760 Workmens Circle.
    Notes: February 27, 1937.
  - Item 2: Souvenir Journal: Fifth Anniversary Banquet., 1939; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 29, 1939.
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings: Sixth Conference Pacific Coast Federation., 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: May 21-22, 1938. Pacific Coast Federation.
  - Item 2: Official Proceedings: Seventh Conference Pacific Coast Federation., 1939; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: May 19-21, 1939. Pacific Coast Federation.
- Box: 4, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Third Annivesary Historical Edition., 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Notes: May 1, 1918. Local 15.
- Box: 4, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Torch., 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1962:July). Reading-Pottstown District.
- Box: 4, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Fifth Anniversary Celebration, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 3, 1941. Scranton District Council.
- Box: 4, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker., 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Notes: Eleven issues, all undated except v.5:no.1 (1940:Dec.). Southern Massachusetts and Rhode Island District.
- Box: 4, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: 1909-1949 40th Anniversary Souvenir Journal., Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Notes: December 22, 1949. Toronto Cloakmakers' Union.
- Box: 4, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Upper South Department, ILGWU., 1956; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Notes: May 10, 1956. Upper South Department.
- Box: 4, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Directory of Offices and Services. Upper South Department., Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Notes: Upper South Department.
- Box: 4, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 75th Conference., 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 13-17, 1975. Upper South Department.
  - Item 2: A Primer on Imports for Garment Workers., 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Author: Martin Lesser; Jerome Breslaw
- Box: 4, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Dixie: Our No.1 Problem., Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: New York Joint Cloak Board., Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: 75,000 Strong., 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Notes: New York Joint Board.
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Notebook of a Garment Worker-Citizen, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Notes: Northeast Department.